<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Injured Workers Unite - Alerts</title>
    <description>Real-time alerts on government data updates, policy changes, and activism opportunities</description>
    <link>https://injuredworkersunite.pages.dev/alerts</link>
    <language>en-CA</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:42:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://injuredworkersunite.pages.dev/alerts-rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Discussion: Canadian farmers to lobby federal government to cap profits of major grocers</title>
      <description>Active discussion in r/onguardforthee</description>
      <link>https://reddit.com/r/onguardforthee/comments/1p7hj7x/canadian_farmers_to_lobby_federal_government_to/</link>
      <guid>REDDIT_1p7hj7x</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:48:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>community</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Federal Data: Wages </title>
      <description>The wages on the Job Bank website are specific to an occupation and provide information on the earnings of workers at the regional level. Wages for most occupations are also provided at the national and provincial level. In Canada, all jobs are associated with one specific occupational grouping which is determined by the National Occupational Classification. For most occupations, a minimum, median and maximum wage estimates are displayed. They are update annually.

If you have comments or ques</description>
      <link>https://open.canada.ca/data/en/dataset/adad580f-76b0-4502-bd05-20c125de9116</link>
      <guid>FED_adad580f-76b0-4502-bd05-20c125de9116</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:21:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>government_data</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Discussion: Got laid off right after I told my work I was ready to come back after sick leave</title>
      <description>Had to go on sick leave after hurting my back at work..(CT warewhouse) was on it for the full 6 months and got a doctors note saying I could go back. 

My back isn&apos;t actually all the way better, still have sciatica but ei ran out so I felt I had no choice.

Anyway, they left me hanging for a few weeks after I told them I was ready to come back then my manager messaged me today saying I was being laid off and that my ROE was already sent for my sick leave. 

So basically I got laid off immediatel</description>
      <link>https://reddit.com/r/legaladvicecanada/comments/1ozv8wj/got_laid_off_right_after_i_told_my_work_i_was/</link>
      <guid>REDDIT_1ozv8wj</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 22:56:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>community</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Discussion: Telus employee fell in my yard</title>
      <description>A Telus employee came to my door and said they had to gain access to my yard to go up a pole in my yard (for some random customers ticket, not ours). This isn’t unusual, they asked if they could go in my yard through my gate and I said yes. For what it’s worth I do have cameras in the front, side and back that are motion activated and have video of them asking for permission. 7 minutes later they fell off their ladder and they called 911 which we only realized when our notifications went crazy o</description>
      <link>https://reddit.com/r/legaladvicecanada/comments/1oy3p5e/telus_employee_fell_in_my_yard/</link>
      <guid>REDDIT_1oy3p5e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 21:39:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>community</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Discussion: I’m getting concerned I will never be able to return back to my pre-injury job.</title>
      <description>I suffered a workplace injury about 9 months ago, where I was immediately receiving WSIB for.  For reference, I suffered from a knee subluxation that doesn’t seem to be recovering very well.
I have been able to do modified duties for the last 4 months, however my employer claims there is nothing for me, and they expect me to come back to my full capabilities to the job I was hired for.
I never passed probation and was only days away from passing my training.  I was there almost 5 weeks before I </description>
      <link>https://reddit.com/r/ontario/comments/1oxfwfm/im_getting_concerned_i_will_never_be_able_to/</link>
      <guid>REDDIT_1oxfwfm</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 02:23:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>community</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Federal Data: Occupational injuries</title>
      <description>The dataset shows claims for occupational injuries registered in one calendar year and admitted no later than March 1 of the following year. 

Occupational injuries are recorded in CNESST systems following the receipt of claims.

These claims represent workers who were covered by the occupational health and safety insurance plan for which the CNESST is responsible.

The _Law on Industrial Accidents and Occupational Diseases_ (LATMP) aims to compensate for occupational injuries and the cons</description>
      <link>https://open.canada.ca/data/en/dataset/0e3ba082-a963-4771-95a2-accc43ae244c</link>
      <guid>FED_0e3ba082-a963-4771-95a2-accc43ae244c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>government_data</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Discussion: Denied extended maternity benefits - Ontario</title>
      <description>Location: Ontario Canada

Myself and 3 other female employees at my work have just started maternity leave.

Our current collective agreement allows 18 weeks of top up pay while on maternity leave.

We are entering a new collective agreement as of January 1, in which maternity top up benefits are extended for 40 weeks.

Our association is stating that the small group of pregnant/new moms who are on leave will NOT be entitled to the terms of the new agreement and will only get the 18 weeks that t</description>
      <link>https://reddit.com/r/legaladvicecanada/comments/1orvbgg/denied_extended_maternity_benefits_ontario/</link>
      <guid>REDDIT_1orvbgg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 17:34:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>community</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill C-1: [object Object]</title>
      <description>Status: undefined. Sponsor: Unknown</description>
      <link>/bills/43-1/C-1/</link>
      <guid>BILL_C-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>legislation</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill C-1: [object Object]</title>
      <description>Status: undefined. Sponsor: Unknown</description>
      <link>/bills/42-1/C-1/</link>
      <guid>BILL_C-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>legislation</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill C-1: [object Object]</title>
      <description>Status: undefined. Sponsor: Unknown</description>
      <link>/bills/40-3/C-1/</link>
      <guid>BILL_C-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>legislation</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill C-1: [object Object]</title>
      <description>Status: undefined. Sponsor: Unknown</description>
      <link>/bills/39-1/C-1/</link>
      <guid>BILL_C-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2006 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>legislation</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill C-1: [object Object]</title>
      <description>Status: undefined. Sponsor: Unknown</description>
      <link>/bills/37-1/C-1/</link>
      <guid>BILL_C-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2001 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>legislation</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>